Guide to the Pulp Science Fiction and Detective Fiction Periodical Collection 1940-1983 MSS 145 MSS.145
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.7 #27, February 1946 (Box 7, Folder 181)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.7 #29, April 1946 (Box 7, Folder 182)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.10 #47, October 1947 (Box 7, Folder 183)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16 #80, July 1950 (Box 7, Folder 184)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16 #81, August 1950 (Box 7, Folder 185)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16 #82, September 1950 (Box 7, Folder 186)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16 #83, October 1950 (Box 7, Folder 187)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16 #84, November 1950 (Box 7, Folder 188)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16 #85, December 1950 (Box 7, Folder 189)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.16, Christmas 1950 (Box 7, Folder 190)
    Special pamphlet with story "Some of My Best Friends"
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.17 #86, January 1951 (Box 7, Folder 191)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.17 #87, February 1951 (Box 7, Folder 192)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.17 #88, March 1951 (Box 7, Folder 193)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.17 #89, April 1951 (Box 7, Folder 194)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.17 #90, May 1951 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.17 #91, June 1951 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.18 #92, July 1951 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.18 #93, August 1951 (Box 7, Folder 198)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.18 #94, September 1951 (Box 7, Folder 199)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.18 #95, October 1951 (Box 7, Folder 200)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.18 #96, November 1951 (Box 7, Folder 201)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.18 #97, December 1951 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.19 #98, January 1952 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.19 #99, February 1952 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.19 #100, March 1952 (Box 7, Folder 205)
    Abraham Lincoln, "The Trailor Murder Mystery"
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.19 #101, April 1952 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.19 #102, May 1952 (Box 8, Folder 207)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.19 #103, June 1952 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.20 #104, July 1952 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.20 #105, August 1952 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.20 #106, September 1952 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.20 #107, October 1952 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.20 #108, November 1952 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.20 #109, December 1952 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.21 #110, January 1953 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.21 #111, February 1953 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.21 #112, March 1953 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.21 #113, April 1953 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.21 #114, May 1953 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.21 #115, June 1953 (Box 8, Folder 220)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.22 #116, July 1953 (Box 8, Folder 221)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.22 #117, August 1953 (Box 8, Folder 222)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.22 #118, September 1953 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.22 #119, October 1953 (Box 8, Folder 224)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.22 #120, November 1953 (Box 8, Folder 225)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.22 #121, December 1953 (Box 8, Folder 226)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.23 #122, January 1954 (Box 8, Folder 227)
    Walt Whitman, "One Wicked Impulse"
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.23 #123, February 1954 (Box 8, Folder 228)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.23 #124, March 1954 (Box 8, Folder 229)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.23 #125, April 1954 (Box 8, Folder 230)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.23 #126, May 1954 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.23 #127, June 1954 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.24 #1, July 1954 (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.35 #4, April 1960 (Box 8, Folder 234)
  - Ellery Queen's Mystery Magazine v.37 #3, March 1961 (Box 8, Folder 235)
    20th Anniversary Issue; Dashiell Hammett, "A Man Named Thin"
- Series IV: Famous Fantastic Mysteries
  An incomplete run of issues from March 1940 to February 1949.
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.1 #6, March 1940 (Box 8, Folder 236)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.4 #3, July 1942 (Box 8, Folder 237)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.4 #6, October 1942 (Box 8, Folder 238)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.5 #1, November 1942 (Box 8, Folder 239)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.5 #2, December 1942 (Box 8, Folder 240)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.5 #3, March 1943 (Box 8, Folder 241)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.5 #4, September 1943 (Box 8, Folder 242)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.5 #5, December 1943 (Box 8, Folder 243)
    Ray Bradbury, "King of the Grey Spaces"
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.5 #6, March 1944 (Box 8, Folder 244)
    G. K. Chesterton, "The Man who was Thursday"
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.6 #1, June 1944 (Box 9, Folder 245)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.6 #2, September 1944 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.6 #3, December 1944 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.6 #4, March 1945 (Box 9, Folder 248)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.6 #5, June 1945 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.6 #6, September 1945 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.7 #1, December 1945 (Box 9, Folder 251)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.7 #2, February 1946 (Box 9, Folder 252)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.7 #3, April 1946 (Box 9, Folder 253)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.7 #4, June 1946 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.7 #5, August 1946 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.8 #1, October 1946 (Box 9, Folder 256)
    H. G. Wells, "The Island of Doctor Moreau"
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.8 #2, December 1946 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.8 #3, February 1947 (Box 9, Folder 258)
    Jack London, "The Star Rover"; G. K. Chesterton, "The Angry Street-A Bad Dream"
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.8 #4, April 1947 (Box 9, Folder 259)
    H. Rider Haggard, "Allan and the Ice-Gods"
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.8 #5, June 1947 (Box 9, Folder 260)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.8 #6, August 1947 (Box 9, Folder 261)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.9 #1, October 1947 (Box 9, Folder 262)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.9 #2, December 1947 (Box 9, Folder 263)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.9 #3, February 1948 (Box 9, Folder 264)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.9 #5, June 1948 (Box 9, Folder 265)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.9 #6, August 1948 (Box 9, Folder 266)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.10 #1, October 1948 (Box 9, Folder 267)
    Ray Bradbury, "The Women"; Ted Sturgeon, "That Low"
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.10 #2, December 1948 (Box 9, Folder 268)
  - Famous Fantastic Mysteries v.10 #3, February 1949 (Box 9, Folder 269)
    Jack London, "The Scarlet Plague"
- Series V: Miscellaneous Magazines
  Collects issues of miscellaneous science fiction pulp magazines.
  - Fantastic Adventures v.8 #4, September 1946 (Box 9, Folder 270)
  - Galaxy v. 34 #1, October 1973 (Box 9, Folder 271)
    23rd Anniversary Issue; Arthur C. Clarke, "Rendezvous with Rama";Harlan Ellison, "Cold Friend"; Ursula K. LeGuin, "Field of Vision"; Ted Sturgeon, "Agness, Accent and Access"
  - Magazine of Fantasy & Science Fiction v.44 #6, June 1973 (Box 9, Folder 272)
  - Magazine of Fantasy & Science Fiction v.55 #4, October 1978 (Box 9, Folder 273)
    29th Anniversary Issue; Thomas Disch, The Man who Had no Idea"; Stephen King, "The Gunslinger"
  - Magazine of Fantasy & Science Fiction v.60 #2, February 1981 (Box 9, Folder 274)
    Stephen King, "The Oracle and the Mountains"; Pat Cadigan, "Second Comings - Reasonable Rates"
  - Magazine of Fantasy & Science Fiction v.65 #4, October 1983 (Box 9, Folder 275)
    34th Anniversary Issue, Ted Sturgeon, "Not an Affair"; Thomas Disch, "Downtown"